Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series VII. Governance, 1952-1992; 14.60 Linear Feet in 35 manuscript boxes.
  Access to this series is restricted until 2027.
  Most of the files in this series are NYU Board of Trustees material dating from 1980 to 1990, including meeting minutes and agendas, President's Reports, committee information, individual member files, and Presidents' Congratulatory files. This series also contains files related to Brademas' trips to Japan, Asia, Poland, Spain, South America, and Yugoslavia on behalf of NYU, which would often involve Board of Trustees members. University Senate meeting files found in this series date from 1980 to 1991 and usually contain minutes, reports, correspondence, and agendas.
  - City Government, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - State Government, 1981-1984 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - State Education Department, 1980-1991 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Applied Science, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 1980-1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Reference Books, Bylaws, 1982-1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- President's Report, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Committees, 1980-1990 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Jeff Viohl Memo, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Academic Affairs Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Academic Affairs Committee, 1984-1991 (Box 67, Folder 6-7)
  - NYU Contributions to Regional Economy -- Preliminary Survey, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Audit Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Child Care, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs Advisory Committee Memo, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Audit Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Audit Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 68, Folder 6-7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Committee on Trustees, 1981-1983 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Committee on Trustees, 1987-1991 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Development Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 69, Folder 6-7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Development Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Report to the Executive Committee, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 70, Folder 3-4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 70, Folder 5-6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Academic Affairs Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Student Affairs Committee, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- President's Quarterly Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Naming Committee, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Joint Trustee Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Naming Gifts Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- General Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees -- General Meetings, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Trustees -- General Meetings, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Agendas, 1987-1989 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Agendas, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1983-1991 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Ackerman, Mona Riklis, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Alexander, Fritz, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Bartley, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Belfer, Arthur, 1982-1983 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Bergreen, Morris, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Bernstein, Richard, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Bobst, Mamdouha, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Boesky, Ivan, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Brimmer, Andrew, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Califano, Joseph, 1982-1990 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Carter, Arthur, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Cherry, James, 1973-1980 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Coles, Jerome S., 1971-1983 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Humanities Council, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 2-3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Creedon, John J., 1978-1984 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Donovan, Hedley, 1964-1979 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Flanagan, Eugene, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Fredericks, Robert, 1986-1988 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Getty, Gordon and Ann, 1985-1987 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Gifford, Bernard, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Gluckman, Lewis, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Greenberg, Alan, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Greenberg, Hank, 1983-1984 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Grunwald, Henry, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Heyman, George, 1978-1989 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Jaffe, Leo, 1972-1982 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Jenrette, Richard, 1975-1978 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Kane, Thomas J., 1980 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Koselanetz, Boris, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Kriser, David S., 1981-1990 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Lachman, Lawrence, 1970-1990 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Leffler, Marvin, 1981-1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Leonard, John, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Lipton, Martin, 1972-1984 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Loeb Family, 1956-1981 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Lubin, Joseph L., 1953-1982 (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Mahoney, David J., 1975-1979 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- McGannon, Donald H., 1970-1981 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Murphy, George A., 1959-1979 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees -- Gifts and Grants -- Nichols, Charles W., 1956-1987 (Box 75, Folder 11-12)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Paul, Herb, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Petrie, Milton J., 1979-1984 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Piel, Gerard, 1975-1981 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Pisani, Bernard J., 1976-1982 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Preston, Lewis, 1977-1981 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Price, Leontyne, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Quartaro, Ignatius, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Rudin, Lewis, 1977-1984 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Sackler, Arthur, 1982-1984 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Sacklad, Maurice, 1952-1983 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Salomon, William, 1971-1979 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Sawhill, John C., 1981 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Schiff, John M., 1952-1982 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Schwartz, Arnold and Marie, 1973-1990 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Seidman, J.S., 1955-1981 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Sharp, Dale E., 1958-1973 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Shimkin, Leon, 1964-1988 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Shipley, Walter, 1983-1984 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Silver, Julius, 1960-1987 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Silverman, Herbert, 1958-1989 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Part I, 1983-1986 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Silverstein, Larry, 1968-1989 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Stern, Leonard, 1974-1988 (Box 78, Folder 2-3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Stillman, Paul, 1953-1985 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Stovall, Robert, 1977-1980 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Strook, Alan, M., 1955-1980 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Taub, Henry, 1975-1980 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Tasco, Frank, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Trustee Committee Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 78, Folder 9-10)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Thiele, Albert, 1954-1983 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Tisch, Laurence, 1959-1988 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Tisch, Preston Robert, 1971-1990 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Tishman, David, 1956-1981 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Wagner, Phyllis and Robert, 1976-1989 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Wallis, Gordon T., 1970-1981 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Weinfeld, Edward, 1974-1980 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Whipple, Taggart, 1969-1990 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Whitehead, Edwin, 1971-1989 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Wright, Robert F., 1979-1987 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees -- Gifts and Grants -- Wrightsman, Charles B., 1962-1986 (Box 79, Folder 10-12)
  - Letter to Gordon M. Ambach, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Merger of Graduate School of Business Administration and Graduate School of Public Administration, Joint Commission, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - Humanities Council, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Long Range Planning Commission, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Security Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Fellowships, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Officers -- President, 1976-1981 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File (MSO), 1982 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Correpondence, Memos, Notes, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 9-14)
  - Correspondence, Reports, Agendas, 1981-1984 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Officers, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - University of Puerto Rico Correspondence, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1984-1986 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Memo to Jeff Viohl, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Reports, Memos, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Officers, President -- Procedures, 1969-1980 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Penthouse Furnishings, 1963-1981 (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
  - Love Letters, 1975-1980 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - NYU Annual Reports, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Tennis Tournament, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Material on Japan, Memos, Correspondence, 1964-1981 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Art, 1970-1982 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Memos on John Brademas Appointment, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Brademas President's Congratulatory, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 9-10)
  - "1492: Crosscurrents of Culture", 1990 (Box 81, Folder 11-12)
  - Brademas President's Congratulatory, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 1-9)
  - Faculty Council Lunch, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Memos, Notes, 1984-1986 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - "1492: Crosscurrents of Culture", 1991 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Bennet -- Presidency, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - German and Greek Trip, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Brademas Trip to Israel, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Dresden and Venice Trip, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Japan Trip, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - England Trip, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Provost and VP for Academic Affairs, 1981-1983 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Vice President's Meeting Agenda, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - University Senate, 1980-1982 (Box 83, Folder 9-10)
  - University Budget Report, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Student Involvement, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Goals, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Organization Charts, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - International Education Report, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Memos about State Grants, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Dean's Meeting Agenda, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Benefits, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Memo on State Budget, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Governor Cuomo, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Memo, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Memo on Dean's Council, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Charles Rangel Correspondence, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- John Chace Armstrong, 1977-1981 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Fisher, Avery R., 1974-1981 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees -- Creedon, John J., 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees -- Heyman Jr. George H., 1986-1987 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Astor, Ms. W. V., 1962-1978 (Box 84, Folder 6-7)
  - Board of Trustees -- Bartley, Robert, 1979-1981 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees -- Gifts and Grants -- Cherry, James R., 1975-1979 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Holman, Wayne J., 1958-1981 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees -- Gifts and Grants -- Donovan, Hedley, 1970-1981 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees -- Greenberg, M.R., 1978-1983 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Hershman, Mendes, 1975-1981 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees -- Gifts and Grants -- Hershman, Mendes, 1975-1976 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees -- Members -- Farkas, Ruth, 1965-1980 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees -- Gifts and Grants -- Farkas, Ruth, 1965-1980 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees -- Jaffee, Leo, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees -- Nichols, C.W. Jr., 1985-1987 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees -- Whipple, Taggart, 1985-1987 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees -- Stern, Leonard, 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees -- Schwartz, Marie, 1985-1987 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees -- Petrie, Milton -- Life Trustee, 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees -- Kriser, David B., 1986-1987 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Agenda, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees -- Boesky, 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees -- Tisch, Laurence A., 1984-1986 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Zerilli-Marimo, Marinccia, 1989-1990 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees -- Zuckerman, Mortimer, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Brademas President's Congratulatory Sample Letters, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Budget Messages, 1980-1982 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Councils and Commissions, Committees and Task Force, 1982-1985 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
  - Councils and Commissions, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Deans' Meeting, 1981-1983 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council, 1980-1982 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Councils and Commissions, Administration Management Council, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Deans' Meeting, 1982-1985 (Box 85, Folder 9-10)
  - Councils and Commissions, Faculty Council, 1981-1984 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Humanities Council, 1981-1983 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Resource Network Council, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 13, Box 86, Folder 1)
  - President's Council on Near Eastern Studies, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Administration Officers -- President Trips, 1981-1983 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Program Proposals and Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Asia, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Trip to Poland, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Memo on Presidential Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Legal Cases RESTRICTED, 1980-1983 (Box 297, Folder 22)
  - Minutes -- Vice President's Weekly Meetings, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - University Senate -- President's Remarks, 1982-1984 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - University Senate -- Committees, 1982-1984 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - University Senate -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 12, Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Student Involvement, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Accreditation, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Universities, 1981-1984 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Higher Education Budget Cuts, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Related to Congress and State Senate, 1981-1982 (Box 87, Folder 7-9)
  - Memos, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with State Government and Members of Congress, 1980-1982 (Box 87, Folder 11-14)
  - Ehrenhalt, Samuel M., 1981 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - China Trip, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 16-17)
  - GVI 1987 City (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Outreach Letter Responses, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Managerial Program for Eastern Europe, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Memorandum to L. Jay Olivia, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Reports, and Newsletters, 1989-1990 (Box 88, Folder 6-8, Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Memo, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Madrid Trip, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Greece and Amsterdam Trip, April 1989 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - France Trip, July 1989 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Ireland, England, France Trip, July 1989 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - RF Trip -- Italy and Africa, September 1989 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Onassis -- Geneva and Madrid Trip, 1989-10-17-1989-10-25 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Greece Trip, March - April 1990 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Eastern European Trip, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Cyprus Trip, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 12, Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Barcelona, Madrid Trip, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Prague Trip, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Union Trip, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Brademas Project -- Europe '92, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 5-7)
  - Madrid, London Trip, November 1990 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Europe 92 Conference Planning Material, 1989-1992 (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
  - Bicentennial of the French Revolution, 1987-1988 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - President's Council on Near Eastern Studies, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - President's Staff Meeting, 1987-01-28 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Academic Computing Facility, and Dean's Meeting Materials, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council, Fall 1988 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Memos, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Bicentennial of the French Revolution, 1987-1988 (Box 92, Folder 1-3)
  - Child Care Committee, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Eastern European Trip, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Moscow Trip, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 7-8)
  - Russian Visa, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - France, Italy, England Trip, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Aspen Institute Berlin, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Europe, Summer, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Brazil Trip, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 5-8, Box 94, Folder 1-2)
  - Buenos Aires Trip, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Africa, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 4-5)
  - President's Holiday Party, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - University Senate -- Anti-Discrimination Policy, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Memo Re: Student Senators-At-Large, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - University Senate -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Student Involvement, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - University Senate -- Executive Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - International Studies, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - University Senate, 1984-1986 (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
  - University Senate -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - University Senate Committees, 1984-1985 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - International Education, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Memo -- Fall Meetings, Other Initiatives, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Accreditation, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - University Senate Meetings, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - University Senate Meetings, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - University Senate Meetings, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - University Senate, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - University Senate -- Financial Affairs Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 96, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Middle States Association, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Study Group on NYU's International Dimension Report, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - NYU-Oxford Faculty Exchange, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Humanities Council, 1984-1985 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Committee for Self-Governance, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council, 1985-1986 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Humanities Council, 1984-1986 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees La Pietra Committee Visit to Italy, 1983-1984 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Egypt Trip, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees -- Committee on Trustees Meeting, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - New York University Consolidated Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Management Council, 1984-1985 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Administration Officers -- Staff Meeting, 1984-1987 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Minutes -- Faculty Council, Board of Trustees, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Publication Subscription-Related, 1981-1985 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - New York Magazine Article Re: Brademas, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Audit Committee, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Use of One Fifth Avenue Residence Apartment 15G, 1983-1986 (Box 97, Folder 8-9)
  - Board of Trustees Members, 1985-1986 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Council on Fiscal and Economic Priorities and Governor Mario Cuomo, 1984-1985 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Re: Penthouse Furnishings, 1984-1985 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Yugoslavia, Austria, Venice Trip, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 14-16)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - President Konstantinos Karamanlis of Greece and Ambassador Petros Molyviates Events, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Meeting, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes and Correspondence, 1989, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - University Senate -- South Africa, 1986-1987 (Box 240, Folder 4-5)
  - Cost Allocation Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 240, Folder 6)
- Series VIII. Governmental Relations, 1961-1990; 8.76 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript boxes.